powerblocktv.com 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy | PowerBlockTV

## Privacy Policy & Legal Disclaimer

* * *

Your right to privacy is very important to RTM Productions, LLC (“RTM”). We are committed to helping you maintain control over your personal data while fostering the growth of a more interactive, engaging, and personalized web and wireless experience. RTM respects your right to control how much information you provide about yourself. The following Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) describes how RTM collects, protects, and uses information we receive from visitors to our web sites, including PowerBlocktv.com, PowerNationTV.com, and RTMTV.com (the “Site(s)”), and from users of our wireless services via cellphones or other wireless devices (the “Service(s)”). By using one of our Sites or Services, you agree to the terms of this Policy. This Policy applies only to information collected through our Sites and Services and not to information collected offline.

_Last Updated: Dec. 6, 2013_

## What Personally Identifiable Information Is Collected

* * *

By “personally identifiable information,” we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, or telephone number. We do not collect personally identifiable information on our Sites or through our Services unless you voluntarily provide information about yourself (a) by setting up an account on one of our Sites or for our Services, (b) via an electronic mail or text message, (c) by filling out one of our online forms, or (d) by purchasing an RTM product from one of our online stores.

No software or hardware techniques are employed to capture a visitor's email address or other personally identifiable information. RTM does not monitor individual traffic patterns on our Sites. RTM and our hosting company may use cookies to collect anonymous, aggregate information or statistics related to Site usage. These statistics indicate the total number of hits, the total number of page hits, the number of kilobytes transferred from our Sites, and the IP address of the visitor. RTM stores cookie information about visitors preferences, recording user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. If we decide to use this information to analyze Web traffic in the future, we will only be able to measure the number of visitors to our Sites and the addresses of the web sites from which our visitors come. Email addresses and other personally identifiable information are not available to us unless you affirmatively supply such information.

Because providing detailed information regarding this Policy when you register or provide information in connection with our Services often proves impractical, you may instead be provided with a short notice that reminds you to refer to this Policy and other relevant information from RTM.

## How the Information You Provide Is Used

* * *

Should you send us your comments or questions via email to any email address provided on one of our Sites or Services, we will only share your communications with our employees or agents most capable of addressing your questions and concerns. We will retain your communication until we have done our very best to provide you with a complete and satisfactory response and then we will either discard it or, in some cases, archive it.

RTM may conduct contests, sweepstakes, and surveys through our Sites and Services. Some of these promotions may be conducted by RTM on behalf of an advertising or promotional partner. Any personally identifiable information that RTM collects from you as part of the promotion will be used by RTM to administer the promotion. For promotions that RTM conducts on behalf of an advertising or promotional partner through the Sites, RTM may share your personally identifiable information with that partner.

We share your personally identifiable information with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, order processing, and sweepstakes fulfillment.

From time to time, our advertising and promotional partners may desire to call your attention to promotions and offers they believe might interest you. If you prefer not to receive direct communications sent by our advertisers or promotional partners, you will be given an opportunity by the advertiser or promotional partner to opt-out of receiving such communications. If you opt-out, you will not receive further email or other communications sent directly by the advertiser or promotional partner, though we may on occasion send you information on their behalf. In all cases, however, we will use your information only as permitted by law.

We may utilize cookies for online advertising. We may also allow “third-party” entities such as ad servers, ad networks and data collection organizations, to place and utilize cookies on RTM Websites. Cookies enable us and other third-parties to present ads to users based on their visit to one of RTM’s Websites and other sites on the Internet.  These third-parties use technology to deliver advertisements that appear on RTM Websites directly to your web browsers. These third-parties automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-parties and RTM Websites to measure the effectiveness of advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  RTM has no access to or control over cookies and technologies that are used by third-party advertisers. RTM's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

From time to time, we may rent our list of customer names collected on our Sites to carefully selected merchandisers or advertisers, but you may choose to opt-out of such rentals by contacting us at [info@rtmtv.com](mailto:info@rtmtv.com) or at the address provided below.

Except as described in this Policy, we will not disclose personally identifiable information unless we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights and property; (c) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of any of our Sites or Services; or (d) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

## Opt-Out

* * *

If you prefer not to receive emails from us, you will be given an opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications in each email that you receive from us. Simply follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of the email message. If you opt-out, you will not receive further email communications from us. If you prefer not to receive communications from us by text message sent to your cellphone or other wireless device, you will be given an opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications in each text message that you receive from us. If you opt-out, you will not receive further text message communications sent by us.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers, networks and data collection organizations for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options or by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) industry website at: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can also be found at the browsers' respective websites.

You also can contact us at [info@rtmtv.com](mailto:info@rtmtv.com), or at the address provided below, indicating that you no longer want to receive email communications relating to one of our Sites or text messages relating to one of our Services.

## Security of Information Sent to Us

* * *

Please note that, unless we expressly advise you otherwise, the email functionality on our Sites does not provide a means for completely secure and private communications between us. Like all unencrypted Internet email communications, your email may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to us. For that reason, to protect your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider to be confidential. While we strive to protect your personal information, RTM cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will use our commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our internal systems. Depending on the nature of the inquiry, your communication may be discarded or archived. If you wish, you may instead contact us via telephone at the number provided in this Policy.

## Disclosure of Customer Information Through Business Transfers

* * *

As we continue to develop our business, we may buy, merge, or partner with other companies or businesses, and in so doing, acquire customer information. In such transactions, customer information may be among the transferred assets. Similarly, in the event that a portion or substantially all of RTM's assets are sold or transferred to a third party, the information you have voluntarily provided to us, including your email address, would likely be one of the transferred business assets.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

* * *

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of children. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. Our Sites and Services are directed to adults at least eighteen years old, and when a user discloses personal information through one of our Sites or Services, the user is representing to us that he or she is an adult. If a child has provided us with personal information, we ask that a parent or guardian email us at [info@rtmtv.com](mailto:info@rtmtv.com) and we will promptly delete the child's information from our records.

## Access and Correction

* * *

You have a right to know about the personal information that RTM has collected from you through our Sites or Services, including the right to correct, amend, or delete the information that RTM has on file if it is incorrect. You may also change the status of whether you wish to receive alerts, newsletters, and communications from RTM at any time. If at any time you wish to exercise these rights, feel free to contact us at [info@rtmtv.com](mailto:info@rtmtv.com) or by phone.

## Special Notification for California Residents

* * *

Under the California Civil Code, residents of the State of California that have provided any personally identifiable information to RTM have the right to request a list of all third parties to which RTM has disclosed personally identifiable information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if RTM has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-in or opt-out choice for use of personally identifiable information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, RTM may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options. RTM qualifies for the alternative option and has adopted a policy of not disclosing the personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option that prevents that information from being disclosed to third parties for those purposes. RTM has established this Policy that provides you with details on how you may either opt-in or opt-out of the use of your personally identifiable information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, please send a request to [info@rtmtv.com](mailto:info@rtmtv.com) with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent.

## Modifications to This Privacy Policy

* * *

By using one of our Sites or Services, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, please do not disclose any personal information through any of our Sites or Services. This Policy and the use of our Sites and Services are governed by Tennessee law. Any claim related to any of our Sites, Services, or this Policy must be brought solely and exclusively in a federal or state court in Nashville, Tennessee within one year after the claim arises, or you agree that such claim will forever be barred. Users of our Sites and Services consent to the jurisdiction and venue of such courts as the most convenient and appropriate for the resolution of disputes concerning this Policy and/or use of our Sites or Services.

Please bear in mind that we may change the content or design of any of our Sites or Services and, consequently, this Policy at any time in the future. Notice of any revisions to this Policy will be posted to this page and on the homepage of each of our Sites, so please revisit this page from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes to this Policy.

RTM welcomes comments and questions about this Policy and about any of our Sites or Services. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information while providing a robust and friendly web environment. Any comments or questions regarding RTM's electronic information privacy practices may be directed to our Webmaster at [info@rtmtv.com](mailto:info@rtmtv.com).com. You may also send a letter to:

  * RTM Productions, LLC
  * 130 Southeast Parkway Court
  * Franklin, TN 37064
  * 615-503-9700
